madhouse909.com 2018-10-03

# Privacy Policy

**ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY**

 **Last updated  **: (03-01-2018)

Madcashcentral Business Links Directory - Internet Advertising, Business & Marketing Blog ("us", "we", or "our") operates http://www.madhouse909.com (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

**Information Collection And Use**  : What we do with the information we gather

We use your Personal Information only for providing us with useful statistics and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, job, address... ( i.e. "Personal Information"). We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

**Internal record keeping** : What it means

\- We may use the information to improve our products and services.

\- We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

\- From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by

  email, phone, fax or mail.

\- We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

\- We may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes.

\- We will never sell your information.

**Log Data**  : What is that ?

Like many site operators, we also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site, that is called ("Log Data").

This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics to collect, monitor and analyze this data… The Log Data section is used for analytics or tracking services in websites or apps, like Google Analytics. For the full disclosure section, see Google's Privacy Policy.

**Communications**  : Why and how we contact our users

We may use your Personal Information to contact you through personalemails, newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that we may find benificiary and/or helpful to our users.

**Cookies**  : How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site. and this may prevent you from taking full advantage of our services and website.

**Security**  : what measures do we use

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of (01-09-2017) and will remain in effect, except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be effective immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the (modified) Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
